# CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

# UX/UI Designer

# CONTACT

Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

A Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

# SKILLS

Design Psychology Front End -

Figma Web Development

Wireframes HTML

Prototyping CSS

User Research JavaScript (JS)

Sketching Node.js

Data Synthesis Git

Usability Testing Bootstrap

Journey Mapping Material UI

Journey Mapping Material
UI Design React.is

UI Design React.js
Adobe Creative Angular.js

EDUCATION

Human Computer
Interaction for UX (Cert.)

MIT

UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

#### PROFILE

Hi, a bit about me I'm a passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill user needs. A capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. A UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain points, and behaviors.

# EXPERIENCE

# **Application Development Analyst**

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
  - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
- Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

#### **Brand Strategist**

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies.
- Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
  - lead to 50% contract signing increase.

#### All-Source Intelligence Technician

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- Designed first ever non-kinetic targeting product in a cross-functional environment.
- Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- Supervision
  - Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
  - Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
  - Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research.